phpjunkyard.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy statement

PHPJunkyard respects the privacy of its' visitors and customers. This privacy statement covers the site **www.phpjunkyard.com**. If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact privacy@phpjunkyard.com and inquire with subject " Privacy concerns ".

## Information Collection and Use

### Information Collection

Klemen Stirn is the sole owner of the information collected on PHPJunkyard. Klemen collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

#### Order

2checkout Inc. is authorized payment processor for PHPJunkyard. They request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

### Information Use

#### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on our site, we can determine whether users were referred by our affiliates. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

#### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google and TxtSwap, our Web advertising partners. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by PHPJunkyard only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable information.

Clear Gifs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same Web site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the Web site would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company. To learn more about our advertising company’s use of clear gifs, please visit Google. 

### Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates

Members registered for our FREE newsletter will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

### Sharing

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

#### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, PHPJunkyard, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards or through e-mail - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

## Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to security@phpjunkyard.com . 

## Supplementation of Information

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

Purchasing History

In order for this Web site to enhance its ability to tailor the site to a user’s preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partner, 2checkout Inc, to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect personal information back with us.

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as email), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the by emailing us at privacy@phpjunkyard.com.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email.

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

privacy@phpjunkyard.com  
https://www.phpjunkyard.com
